[
    {
        "question": "Nuage",
        "options": [ "Sky", "Cloud", "Breeze", "Storm" ],
        "answer": "Cloud"
    },
    {
        "question": "Oiseau",
        "options": [ "Wolf", "Sheep", "Bird", "Mouse" ],
        "answer": "Bird"
    },
    {
        "question": "Soleil",
        "options": [ "Moon", "Star", "Sun", "Planet" ],
        "answer": "Sun"
    },
    {
        "question": "Fleur",
        "options": [ "Field", "Flower", "Grass", "Leaf" ],
        "answer": "Flower"
    },
    {
        "question": "Ã‰cole",
        "options": [ "Church", "House", "Shop", "School" ],
        "answer": "School"
    },
    {
        "question": "Voiture",
        "options": [ "Bike", "Car", "Boat", "Plane" ],
        "answer": "Car"
    },
    {
        "question": "Eau",
        "options": [ "Air", "Fire", "Earth", "Water" ],
        "answer": "Water"
    },
    {
        "question": "Arbre",
        "options": [ "Bush", "Forest", "Tree", "Grass" ],
        "answer": "Tree"
    },
    {
        "question": "Neige",
        "options": [ "Rain", "Snow", "Ice", "Wind" ],
        "answer": "Snow"
    },
    {
        "question": "Chanson",
        "options": [ "Film", "Book", "Song", "Game" ],
        "answer": "Song"
    }
]